啊  天呀  真不敢相信  弟弟你已经结婚了
Oh my God! I can’t believe my little brother is married!
你们俩为什么不告诉我你们准备结婚
You guys, why didn’t you tell me you were eloping?
因为我们之前也没有想过结婚这事  那天我们去法院  我们正在吃午饭
'Cause it just sorta happened, y'know we were at the courthouse, we were having lunch…
等等  你们去法院做什么呀
Wait, wait, why were you at the courthouse?
我们去吃午饭呀
We were having lunch.
然后  我们突然之间意识到
Yeah and then all of the sudden we were like,
嘿   我们正在法院吃饭  吃完饭我们去登记结婚吧
"Hey! Y'know, we’re here, having lunch let’s get married! right!
哇  一年半以前我甚至都不知道自己有个弟弟  现在我还有弟媳了
Wow, a year and a half ago I didn’t even know I had a brother, and now I have a sister too.
真是太棒了
Oh, it's so great.
好了  够了
Okay. Okay.
别再亲了
Stop it, don't. So,
我得送你们新婚礼物才行
I'll get you a gift now.
你们需要什么吗
Is there anything you need?
嗯  有啊
Uh, yeah.
我们俩一直努力想要个孩子  嗯  几乎从我们订婚那天就开始了  我们非常着急
We've been trying to get pregnant. uh pretty much ever since we got engaged, we'd get a jump on things,
你也知道  我们都不年轻了
y'know no one's getting any younger. Ha-ha-ha.
但情况是  嗯  她不能怀孕
Because the thing is, um, we're not able to, you know, uh, conceive.
我们什么方法都试过了  也去看了不少医生
And we've tried everything, we've seen a bunch of doctors.
医生说了  我们有孩子的唯一的机会就是
Yeah, and they-and they say that our-that our only chance to have a baby ...
把我的精子和她的卵子  放在一个器皿里
...is that if they take my sperm, her egg, and put it together in a dish...
再放进另一个女孩的子宫里
...and put it into another girl.
因此我们在想  你可不可以成为那个女生  把它放进去
So we were wondering if you could be that girl that we could put it into.
那真是一个美好的礼物
That's a really nice gift.
我刚刚还以为是要放到酱油壶里呢
I was thinking of a gravy boat.
老友记  第四季 第14集  菲比外借子宫
The One With Phoebe’s Uterus
主演：珍妮佛安妮斯顿
主演：寇妮考克斯
主演：丽莎库卓
主演：麦特勒布兰
主演： 马修派瑞
主演： 大卫修蒙
嘿  快来看看  快来看看  猜我找到什么工作了
Hey! You guys! Check it out, check it out! Guess what job I just got.
不知道  但是Donald Trump（赌场大亨）想让他的蓝色运动夹克变黑所以借你穿脏点.
I don't know, but Donald Trump wants his blue blazer black.
什么
What?
我是说要回  他想要回他的夹克
Blue blazer back. He wants it back.
你刚才是说 "变黑"   他为什么想把他的蓝色夹克变黑呢
You said "black." Why would he want his blue blazer black?
你知道我的意思
Well, you know what I meant.
不是  你弄混了
No,You messed it up.
你真蠢
You're stupid.
乔伊  你找到什么工作了
So what job did you get Joe?
博物馆里的解说员   罗斯帮我争取到的
Oh, ah, tour guide at the museum. Yeah, Ross got it for me.
要成为解说员  不得是恐龙或者是历史专家吗
Well, how can you be a tour guide, don't you have to be a dinosaur expert or something?
不  其实不用  他们会把资料都给你
No, not really. They give you all the information.
制片：史塔德帝文斯
嗯  就跟背剧本一样
it's uh, it's like memorizing a script.
"在您的左边  您看到的是暴龙  一种来自侏罗纪的肉食动物."
"And on your left, you have Tyrannosaurus Rex, a carnivore from the Jurassic period.
编剧：赛斯寇兰
不赖嘛
Very nice.
嗯  其实暴龙是来自白垩纪
Yeah, actually, Joey, it's the Cretaceous Period.
导演：大卫史坦伯
是  但我念得是侏罗纪
Yeah but, I can pronounce Jurassic.
嗨
Hey!
你们猜怎么了  法兰克和艾莉丝结婚了
Guess what. Frank Jr., and Alice got married!
啊  天啊
Oh, my God!
还有  还有  他们要生小孩了
And! And, they’re gonna have a baby!
还有  还有  他们还要用我的子宫来生
And! And, they want me to grow it for them in my uterus.
天啊  你没开玩笑吧
My God! Are you serious?
是啊
Yeah.
你在考虑和自己的弟弟上床
You're thinking of having sex with your brother?
你好恶心  才不是
Ewww! And "Oh no!"
他们只是要找我代孕
It's—they just want me to be the surrogate.
用他们的精子和卵子  我只是烤炉  面包完全是他们的
It's her-it's her egg and her sperm, and I'm-I'm just the oven, it's totally their bun.
那你答应了没
What did you tell them?
他们说先让我考虑考虑  但是这有什么可考虑的呢
Well, they said that I had to think about it first, but what is there to think about?
这是我能送出的最好的礼物
I'm gonna be giving them the greatest gift you can possibly give.
你将要帮他们怀孩子  还给他们一台索尼PS
You'll carry their child, and get them a Sony PlayStation?
亲爱的  为他们这么做  的确是一件惊人的喜事
Honey, this really is an incredible thing to do for them,
但是有些事你得再想想
But there are things to think about.
是呀  你将要怀孕  是怀孕呀
Yeah, you'd be pregnant. I mean pregnant.
我知道啊
I know.
菲比  你的身体将接受一段可怕的经历
Pheebs, you're talking about putting your body through an awful lot,
我是说  如晨吐  嗯  分娩
I mean morning sickness, uhh, labour,
还全都是为了别人
and it's all for somebody else!
是啊  你的要点是什么
Yeah. What's your point?
我刚才说的就是啊
Well, the stuff I just mentioned.
不知道我这辈子会不会那么做
Wow! I don't know if I could ever do that.
我一直在想  如果我第一次怀孕  一定是为一个我爱的人
Y'know I always figured the first time I had a baby was with somebody I love
而且我得照顾…
and that baby would be a
那个孩子
...a keeper.
我当初想做家具时  你们可是很支持我的
Y'know you guys were a lot more supportive when I wanted to make denim furniture.
不是  菲比  如果你决定要这么做  我们当然会全力支持你的
No, Pheebs, listen, if you decide to do this, we'll be supportive like crazy.
我们只是要你考虑清楚
We just want you to think it through.
对  亲爱的  也许你可以和生过孩子的人聊聊  例如你妈妈
Yeah, honey, maybe you can talk to somebody who's had a baby. Like your mom.
我妈才没生过小孩呢  不过我的生母有
My mom never gave birth. Oh! But my birth mom did!
（中央咖啡馆）
我喜欢你的小屁屁  可以让我带去上班吗
I love this tushy! Can I take it to work with me?
哦  没问题  反正不是我的 是买裤子附赠的
Oh, yeah, sure. It's not mine anyway. It came with the pants.
我嫉妒死了
I am so jealous.
你们俩正在那个阶段  对吧
You guys are really right…there aren’t you?
是啊
Yes.
哪个阶段
Right where?
热恋期  一天到晚的甜言蜜语
In the beginning where it's all sex and talking...
不眠不休的性生活  还有
...and sex and talking.and…
聊天的部分很棒
Yeah, you-you gotta love the talking.
那上床呢
And the sex?
好  我们还没上过床
All right, we haven’t had sex yet.
对  那又能怎么样  你知道  这次恋爱对我来说很特殊
Okay, What's the big deal? Y'know? This is special,
我想充分培养感情  再更上一层楼
and I want our love to grow before we move on to the next level.
钱德  你那么做好体贴呀
Oh, Chandler, that is so nice.
是很体贴
That is really nice...
骗人
...lying!
不可能是你说的那个原因  为什么
No way is that the reason. Why?
只是因为你还不够成熟  去理解像这样的事情
Just because you're not mature enough to understand something like that?!
不  罗斯说的对  我是在骗人
No, he's right, I'm totally lying.
那真相是什么
Then what is it?
因为Kathy的前任男友是乔伊
Well, Kathy's last boyfriend was Joey.
你担心自己…技不如人
And you're afraid you won't be able to fill his shoes?
不  我担心自己床上功夫没他行
No, I'm afraid I won't make love as well as him.
对  我刚刚在用比喻
Yeah, I was going for the metaphor.
对  我刚刚是直接说出来
Yes, and I was saying the actual words.
没事啦  乔伊交过一卡车女友  这也不表示他床功一流
So big deal, so Joey's had a lot of girlfriends, it doesn't mean he's great in bed.
我们的房只隔着一面墙
We share a wall.
因此  要么他在床上极强悍  要么就是她喜欢附和他
So either he's great in bed, or she just likes to agree with him a lot.
亲爱的  她和你将会不同的  有爱做基础的性会更棒
Sweetie, with you it's gonna be different.The sex is gonna be great, 'cause you-you guys are in love.
是吗  是啊
Yeah? Yeah.
钱德  你大胆的向前
Just go for it Chandler.
对  试试看就知道了
Yeah, you should, really.
那好吧  我这就去和女朋友睡觉
All right. all right, I'll sleep with my girlfriend.
但我这么做  全是为了你们
But I'm just doing it for you guys.
接下来这头乳齿象  是来自侏罗纪中后期
Okay, now the Mastodon is from the semi-late Jurassic period.
乳齿象不是来自上新世吗
Isn't the mastodon from the Pliocene Epoch?
嘘嘘  这里是博物馆  不许讲话
Shh.This is a museum, no talking.
这里的就是…
Right down here we have...
大脚
...a large foot.
这位是罗斯盖勒
And over here we have Ross Geller.
大家挥手和罗斯打招呼  说 "嗨"
Everyone wave "hi" to Ross.
罗斯是博物馆里最重要的科学家之一  快看看他  工作多努力
Ross is one of our most important scientists, look at him, hard at work.
好  继续参观
Okay, moving right along.
走吧
Come on.
门开着呢  进来吧
It's open! Come in!
抱歉迟到了  没关系
I'm sorry I'm late. That's okay.
我正好有时间给乳头上釉
it gave me time to finish glazing my nipples.
哇  你为了见客还真是拼命
Wow! You really go all out when you're expecting company.
没有  我刚刚在做陶器
No, I was working on my pottery.
哇  哦
Oh! Oh!
我不知道你会做…罐子
Oh! I didn't know that you did pot.
对  大部分是裸体的  它结合了我的两大嗜好  陶器和色情艺术
Well, yeah, Mostly nudes. It combines my two passions: Pottery and erotica.
哦  就叫 "情色陶器" 吧
Ooh, erotiery!
不错
Hey! Okay!
谢谢你来看我  我只是
Well thanks for coming out to see me. I just
我只是觉得生小孩这件事  还是当面聊比较好
I just thought it would be a very good idea to talk about this baby stuff in person.Okay.
菲比  我真的认为你不应该那么做
I really don't think it's a very good idea, Phoebe.
为什么
Why not?
因为  你最后还得送走孩子
Well, because you'd be giving up a baby,
我不知道…
And I really don't...
我不知道怎么说才能让你理解
I don't know if there's anything I can say...
送走孩子会有多么痛苦
...that could make you understand the pain of giving up a baby.
所以
So...
不   我了解那种痛苦  不要伤害小狗
No, no, I understand the pain. Don't-don't hurt the puppy.
不  不是啦  这小狗是你的了
No, no. The puppy is yours.
我有小狗
Oh, I get a puppy!
对  但你只能拥有三天
Well, yeah! I mean yeah, but only for three days.
为什么
Why?
我知道我没有权利像母亲一样管你  但是
Y'know. I realise I don't have any right to start get all parenty on you and everything now,
菲比  麻烦别看小狗  看着我  这事非常重要
uhh… Phoebe, would you please look at me and not the puppy, it's very important.
好
Okay.
我是说  我知道自己以前做了什么
I mean, I know what I'm talking about.
我抛弃了2个孩子
I gave up two babies.
而且我真的希望  当时身边能有个前辈告诉我
and I only wish I had someone there that had given up babies, that could tell me...
抛弃自己的孩子会有多痛苦
...how terrible it is to give up babies.
我只是在想  那么做的后果将会是遗恨终生
I just think that, it would be something you will regret every single day for the rest of your life.
你到时候送走这条小狗的痛苦
So however hard it is for you to give up this puppy...
还不及送走孩子的百万分之一
...it would be a million times harder to give up a child.
早知道  我真不应该先给你小狗
I really shouldn't have given you the puppy first.
你介意坐在别处吗  我帮朋友罗斯留着这个座呢
Uhh, do you mind sitting there. I'm saving this seat for my friend Ross.
你是说盖勒博士
You mean Dr. Geller?
博士  我不知道他还有一个绰号
Doctor? Wow! I didn't know he had a nickname.
他才不会坐在这里
Oh, he won't sit here.
穿白袍的都会坐在那里
Only the people in the white coats sit over there,
穿蓝色外套的就只能坐这里
and only the people in the blue blazers sit here.
为什么这样
Well, how-how come?
这里就是这样
That's just the way it is.
太荒唐啦
That's crazy.
在完美的世界里  这或许是有些荒唐  一个不分研究员和解说员的世界
Maybe it's crazy in a perfect world: A world without lab coats and blazers.
但你不是活在完美世界里   你是在这个博物馆
But you not in a perfect world. You in a museum now.
看到那戴眼镜的科学家没
See that scientist in the classes,
他和我以前在小学时总是在一起玩  现如今却....
he and I used to play together all the time in grade school, but now…
彼德  嗨  彼德
Peter! Hey, Peter!
我是朗姐  我们是同届的啊
It's me, Rhonda from P.S. 129?
亏我把布丁分你吃过
I shared my pudding with you, man!
我还把点心棒送给你吃
I gave you my snack pack!
看到没  他甚至假装没听到我说的话
See? He pretend he don't even hear me!
我想大家都在假装没听到你说话
I-I think everybody's pretending they don't hear you.
总之  我不了解你  我才不管什么制服和餐桌的分别的事
Anyway, look, I don't know about you and your jackets and your separate tables, ...
不过罗斯是我最好的朋友之一
...but Ross is one of my best friends,
而且我要是为他留了座位  我告诉你  他肯定会坐在这里
and if I save him a seat, I'm telling you, he will sit in it!
罗斯  罗斯
Ross. Ross.
这里  我帮你留了个座位
Over here, man! I-I saved you seat.
不用  我坐这边很好  我一会去找你
That's okay, I'm cool over here. I'll catch up with you later, Joey.
这个位置有人坐了
Op, this is saved.
礼品店的
Gift shop.
今天在自助餐厅的事  我真的  真的非常抱歉
Hey, uh, I'm really, really sorry about what happened in the cafeteria today.
没什么  嘿   真的  你是迫不得已  对吧
It's no big deal. Hey, y'know, you do what you gotta do. Right?
不只是我而已  我是说科学家和解说员从来都不坐在一起
But hey, it's not just me, I mean the scientists and the tour guides never sit together.
随便你啦
Whatever.
到处都这样  摩妮卡  帮我说说话啊
It's like that everywhere, Joey! Okay, Mon, back me up here.
在你工作那里  服务员也是和服务员一起吃饭  对吧
Where you work the uh, waiters eat with the waiters, right?
并且厨师和厨师一起吃  对吧
And the chefs eat with the other chefs, right?
我自己在走廊里自己吃饭  因为人人都讨厌我
I eat by myself in the alley, because everybody hates me.
罗斯  你听我说
Look, Ross.
真的  真的没什么
really it's-it's no big deal.
你知道你穿白袍  我穿蓝色制服
Y'know you wear a white coat, I wear a blue blazer,
如果那代表着我们不能在单位成为朋友  那就这样吧
If that means we can't be friends at work, then so be it.Y'know,
我理解
hey I understand. Y'know?
嘿  当我在舞台上  你在观众席上  我也没和你说话  对吧
Hey, when I'm in a play and you're in the audience, I don't talk to you, right?
所以  你知道  没事
So it's, you know, it's, uh, cool.
明天见
I'll see you tomorrow.
对  当他在舞台上时是没有和我们说话  但他确实挥过手
Yeah, when we're in the audience he doesn't talk to us, but he does wave.
嗨
Hi.
菲比  为什么对着卡尔马登(电影演员)唱歌
Why's Phoebe singing to Karl Malden?
我想现在又到遛狗的时间了
Ooh, y'know what, I think it's time for puppy to go out again.
走  我们去阳台  什么
Come on, let's go to the balcony. What?
哦  是街道  快点  我们上街去
Umm, the street. Come on, let's go to the street.
听着  我回来之前别去阳台
Ooh, listen, don't go onto the balcony until after I get back.
怎么样  你做了吗
So did you do it?
是  是  我们做爱了
Yes, yes, we had the sex.
糟糕  不好喔
Uh-oh. It was bad?
还可以  但是她附和我的程度  不像附和乔伊那样强烈
It was fine, y'know? But she didn't agree with me as strongly as she agreed with Joey.
感觉像是 "我了解  无所谓"
She was more like, "I see you point, I'm all right with it."
没关系  你们毕竟是第一次嘛  不可能一开始就和谐的
Well, it was the first time. Y'know, there's not always a lot of agreement the first time.
对啊  通常都是女人觉得还不够和谐  男人却很快就满足了
Yeah. Not for girls, anyway. Guys agree like that.
看  你得帮帮我  行吗
Look, you have to help me. Okay?
我是说…
I mean...
我知道该做些什么  我也知道哪里总是让人感觉美妙
I know what to do with a woman, y'know, I know where everything goes, it's always nice.
但我需要知道…
But I need to know ...
要使得她从美妙到…
...what makes it go from nice to...
"天呀  那家伙让她欲仙欲死"
..."My God! Somebody's killing her in there!"
我来告诉你  很多男人不知道的 "密笈"
All right, I'm gonna show you something a lot of guys don't know.
瑞秋  麻烦把那本子给我
Rach, give me that pad, please?
好吧
All right.
来
Now.
你不用画的那么具体  哇  身材惹火
Look, You don't have to draw an actual... Whoa, she's hot!
好  每个人都知道的  基本的性敏感带
Now everybody knows the basic erogenous zones.
第1个  第2个  第3个
You got one, two, three...
第4个…
...four...
第5个  第6个还有第7个
...five, six and seven.
一共有7个
There are seven?
让我看看
Let me see that.
对   没错
Oh, yeah.
那里也算一个
That's one?
那个还是一个挺重要的呢
It's kind of an important one!
哦  什么啊  我看颠倒了
Oh, y'know-y'know what, I was looking at it upside down.
有时候反过来也不错
Well, y'know, sometimes that helps.
男人大多数爱抚过1-2-3   就直接跳到第七个  结束比赛
Now, most guys will hit uh, 1-2-3 and then go to 7 and set up camp.
那样不好吗
That's bad?
如果你去迪斯尼游乐园   你不会整天都玩过山车吧
Well if you go to Disneyland, you don't spend the whole day on the Materhorn.
如果那是象7那样的东西  也许你可能会那么做
Well you might if it were anything like 7!
嗯  重点是慢慢来
All right uh, the important thing is to take your time,
你得把所有的敏感部位都照顾到
You want to hit them all...
让它们全部保持兴奋状态  就像走路那样紧绷脚趾
... and you mix them up. You gotta keep them on their toes.
脚趾
Oh, toes!
对一些人有用
For some people.
好吧
All right.
你可以从一点点1
You could, uh, start out with a little one.
再来2
A two.
1  2  3 搭配
A one, two, three.
一个3
A three.
一个5
A five.
一个4
A four.
来个3和2
A three, two.
2  再配个2  4  6
Two. A two, four, six.
2  4  6
Two, four, six.
4  2
Four. Two.
2  4和7
Two. Four, seven!
5配7   6配7
Five, seven! Six, seven!
7  7
Seven! Seven!
7  7  7
Seven, seven, seven!
Seven!
盖勒博士  这里有个座位
Dr. Geller, there's a seat over here.
菲利普斯博士  谢谢你
Thank you, Dr. Phillips.
但我的午餐…
But I'm having my lunch...
要在这张桌子上吃  中间这一张
...at this table. Here in the middle.
就坐在这里吃午餐
I'm having lunch right here,
和我的好朋友乔伊一起吃
...with my good friend Joey,
如果他愿意和我坐在一起
If he'll sit with me.
盖勒博士  我跟你坐
I will sit with you, Dr. Geller.
你们知道吗…
You know...
我们在自然史博物馆工作
...we work in a museum of natural history.
然而有一件事…
And yet, there is something...
却很不自然
...unnatural...
我们吃中饭的方式很不自然
...about the way we eat lunch.
现在  我环顾这间餐厅  你知道我看到什么吗  是隔阂
Now, I look around this cafeteria, and y'know what I see, I see-I see division.
穿白大褂和蓝制服的人之间的隔阂
Division between people in white coats and people in blue blazers.
我扪心自问 "天啊  为什么会这样"
and I ask myself,  "My God, why?"
我建议大家脱掉…
Now, I say we shed these-these coats...
造成我们隔阂的这些外套
...that separate us.
真诚的相互了解
And we get to know the people underneath.
我是罗斯
I'm Ross!
我离过婚  还有个小孩
I'm divorced and I have a kid!
我是乔伊   我是个演员
I'm Joey! I'm an actor!
我对恐龙一窍不通
I don't know squat about dinosaurs!
我是泰德   一个月前才搬来  纽约真是吓坏我了
I'm Ted, and I just moved here a month ago, and New York really scares me.
大家都这样才对  秦德  你要坚持到底
All right, there you go! Yeah, you hang in there Teddy!
我是安德鲁
I'm Andrew.
这颗梨我没付钱
And I didn't pay for this pear.
好  真有你的
Okay. good-good for you.
我是朗姐  我隆过胸
I'm Rhonda! And these aren't real!
朗姐…
Wow, Rhonda.
我是史考特  帮史考特加油
I'm Scott. Yeah, okay, Scott!
我在离开一个房间之前  一定要连续开灯关灯17次
And I need to flip the light switch on and off 17 times before I leave a room...
不然我全家都会死光光
...or my family will die.
我妈妈随时要来领走它
My mom's gonna be here any minute.
我没办法  我确实舍不得
I can't do this, I can't give him up.
不对  我可以
Yes, no. I can.
我不想那么做
I don't want to.
但是我可以
But I can.
不行
No.
我看不下去了  就好像在看《苏菲的选择》
Oo, I can't watch this, It's like Sophie's Choice.
我从没看过那部电影
You know, I never saw that.
其实很普通一般而已
Oh, it was only okay.
我办不到
I can't do this.
我妈妈说的对  如果我连一条狗都舍不得
My mom was right. If I can't-if I can't give him up,...
怎么可能送走自己生的孩子
...then there's no way I can give up a baby.
唉  老天啊  法兰克和艾莉丝听了一定会非常的沮丧
Ohh, God, Frank and Alice are gonna be so crushed.
还有什么  我还能给他们什么  肾
What-what else, what else can I give 'em—a kidney!
我们刚刚散步走到这里  因此
Uhh, we were just in the neighbourhood, so…
对  我们路过进来看看  想让你知道  不想让你有什么压力
Yeah, so we just thought we'd stop by and let you know there's still no pressure.
没有啊
None.
但是你要是有什么想和我们说  我们就坐在那里喝咖啡
But if there was something you wanted to tell us, we're just gonna be right over there having coffee.
好
Okay.
这个小家伙是谁
Oh, who's this little guy?!
真可爱  让我想起我的老狗肿瘤
He's so cute! He reminds me of my old dog, Tumor.
你太漂亮啦  真想把你带回家
You are so precious, I could just take you home.
嘿  为什么不呢
Hey, why don't you?
你是说真的
Are you serious?
是啊
Uh-huh. Yeah.
多谢了
Oh, thanks.
你在干嘛  这样不会让我难过
What are you doing? No, I'm really okay with this.
你知道为什么吗  看看他们
You know why? Because look at them.
看他们有多幸福
Look how happy they are.
是我给他们带来快乐  所以…
And I made that, so... Y'know
我知道送走自己生出来的孩子  一定会难上百万倍
it's gonna be like a million times harder to give up a baby but, oh my God,
但那时的快乐会让我感觉伟大一百万倍  对吧
it's gonna feel like a million times better, right?
我决定了  我要怀你们的孩子
I wanna do this.I wanna carry your baby.
太感激你了
Thank you so much!
你不知道这对我们来说意味着什么
You don't know what this means to us.
天啊  我都快哭了
Oh my God, I think I'm gonna cry!
太伟大了
It's going to be so great.
嗨
Hi.
怎么回事   我把小狗给了他们
What's going on? Oh, I-I gave them the puppy
看他们高兴成那样   我决定帮他们怀孩子
and it made them so happy that I decided I’m gonna carry their baby.
但是菲比  不-不-不  我知道
But Phoebe... No-no-no, I know,
我们是不同的人
but you and I are different people though,
而且情况和你当年也完全不同
and this is a totally different situation,
而且我知道我以后不会为这事遗憾
and I know that I am not gonna regret this
喔  我-我完全理解
Oh, I-I-I understand all that,
但是  那是我的小狗
but it's just—that was my puppy.
你这辈子会不会帮别人怀孕
Would you ever be a surrogate for anyone?
那要看是谁要我帮忙
It depends on who asked.
如果那个人是我呢
What if I asked?
摩妮卡  我当然愿意啊
Oh, Mon, sure!
真的  是啊
Really? Yes.
你不是真的求我吧   不是
You’re not asking are you? No.
我当然帮你  一定帮
Yes. Totally.
谢谢你...
Thank you! Thank you!
谢谢你
Thank you!
太谢谢你了
Yes, thank you!